Hello, my name is Mao Iyoi.
I am Mukai Hazuki.
I am Mao Tomisaka.
Today, what a surprise, I'm here at the Nogizaka Costume Warehouse.
Amazing. I'm so happy.
Um, I heard that none of the Nogizaka members have joined.
You just heard that, didn't you?
That's great.
I'd like to see more.
Let's see.
I'm too scared when I eat my pirate bento.
That's scary.
No way.
I've never seen this before.
Wait, no.
I saw it.
I can't believe I'm seeing this.
That's amazing.
I'll open it.
Hohoho.
Go.
Wow.
That's great.
I feel like a princess.
Wow, that oak closet is too big.
Wow.
Now that's what I'm talking about.
We've worn these uniforms before.
I wonder if they have old ones.
Uniforms we've never worn.
We've never worn the ones before we came here.
I haven't.
Wow, that brings back memories!
It's true.
Wow, all those skirts.
I touched them so much.
They're so cute.
That skirt.
I wore that skirt in my audition for the third season.
Oh, really?
We didn't.
You know, the ones you were wearing before you floated?
That's right.
That's what happened.
It's the kind of skirt I used to wear.
I'm so excited.
It's like a great encore.
The third single.
It's true.
The old ones were short, weren't they?
That's true.
It's a Force blazer.
It's true.
This one.
I've seen some of the older students wearing them.
It's got the Nogizaka logo on it.
It's not as big as it is now.
That's right.
It's a cake.
No, no, no.
There were originally three sizes of emblems
There are three kinds of emblems originally.
It's not a cake.
No, it's not.
Wow.
That's nice.
I like it... it's what you want.
Sailor.
Wait, I didn't know there was a frill here.
It's a white one.
She's cute.
From Girls Rule.
Cute.
White.
I'm too scared to eat lunch with this one.
They'll get mad at me.
Oh, good, they know.
We're pretty good, aren't we?
We pay attention to the names, don't we?
We do.
I was so happy to be able to wear my senior's dress.
I was so happy to be able to wear my seniors' clothes.
I was so excited, Mr. Ishio told me not to get excited.
"Don't be so excited!
He's too cute.
That made you happy.
I realized I had a crush on you.
I've always had a crush on you.
I know.
I'd like to try it on.
It's so cute.
It's so quick.
So cute.
This length is really beautiful.
I have an image of them all together.
Taller girls are a little bit...
I wonder if it's because it's longer.
I wonder if that's true.
You know, I had a uniform for the first season.
I had a uniform, remember?
I hadn't worn it in a while, and it was so short.
It's grown long.
That's amazing.
I wore it around the beginning.
It's gotten a lot shorter.
That's right.
It's growing.
This is summer swing.
Summer
Summer-inspired materials and colors.
So cute!
This is Ms. Ikuta's image.
It's true.
Compared to her early days
A little longer
I'm sure of it.
The change of the times...
Maybe it's the sun.
Sailor type
Cute sunnokka
It looks like there's a pattern to this, too.
It's true.
With lines or without lines
or not.
It's so cute.
I can't wait to find out.
This one looks the warmest.
Looks warm.
What's this one from?
It's a halcyon.
The shape of the jacket.
It's very distinctive.
Even the back.
Like a cicada.
Cicada? What do you call it?
It's so cute.
This is so cute.
It's a summery fabric.
It's so cute.
It means goodbye.
What does goodbye mean?
This is where I've come from.
I see.
Okay.
I've been here maybe once or...
The first time.
When I was allowed to appear in Nogizaka Construction Workshops.
It was this one.
A little bit.
This is Nogizaka's
That's great.
I'm watching this.
I'm looking at this.
It's so tight.
It's got this kind of texture.
It looks like it's been used a long time.
This is a little too rare.
I love it.
It's too rare.
No way.
Stupid.
Stupid Hashimoto-san!
It was Mr. Hashimoto.
This is still here.
Ouch.
I'm back in uniform.
I miss it.
And it's so noble.
I can't show it off at all.
Wow, the fabric is so different from before.
It's so stiff.
It's totally different from before.
The fabric is like this.
It's so cute.
But I really can't eat this for dinner.
I can't eat this.
It's too scary!
The first captain, Reika Sakurai, used to spill food all over it.
I see.
I feel a little relieved.
She even turned her bento over neatly in her uniform's lap.
Ew.
I see.
I'm very attached to it.
Runaway Water.
Naoki Oda's got it.
Yes, I do.
It's this color.
The lighter one.
It's just a little different.
They're really slightly different.
I'll show you your guess at once.
bamboo, bamboo, bamboo
bamboo
That's it.
Okay, let's see.
It'll be great if you hit it.
It'd be great if I hit it.
Please follow me to dinner.
One hundred times.
Jeez, jeez, jeez, jeez.
Yes, yes...
Hello, Yodaa.
It was Yodaa.
Yodaa?
It's Yodaa's.
It wasn't Hazuki's.
But let's go out to eat.
I promise.
Let's go.
Warm... like chocolate.
Like chocolate.
It's so cute.
When I was in this outfit...
They were doing a Valentine's Day show.
I saw it.
I did.
Oh, my God.
I miss it.
The Valentine's Day project... the third term students giving out the valentines.
I was really impressed with this outfit.
This is Synchronicity.
It's so cute!
So cute!
Nananki is adorable.
She's so cute!
Stylish
It's so wrinkled
Oh, I see.
The gown maker told me not to sit on it too tight.
It's going to get wrinkled.
Because of your name...
This one...
It's cute.
This one.
Selfish.
Oh, wow.
The material.
Oh, yeah, and the fabric.
Crunchy.
Crunchy, crunchy, crunchy.
When you turn it...
It would wrinkle up too much.
I had to hold it back while I danced.
Oh, wow!
We're going to hear more and more episodes of this uniform from here on out.
It's true.
There's Mr. Dough.
It's so cute.
There's a Nogizaka logo on the button.
Oh!
Nogizaka46
This is
Sing out
Oh okay
This one has a ribbon that goes clorin.
I always had to adjust it right up until the last minute.
That's right.
It's been a long time.
Is this Shikisei's?
I think it's a different one.
Is this Dawn?
Dawn.
It's from the same time period.
It's the same time of year.
I was wearing short sleeves the other day.
It's definitely getting colder.
Yeah, it's longer now that winter's here.
Summer version and
Yeah, happy protective colors.
Protective colors.
Wow, that brings back memories.
I remember when the older students wore these.
Oh, and this is Mr. Shiki.
I loved it.
Stir Tan
The image of Stir Tan
You're right.
This color is so cute!
So cute!
Seeing it on film is totally different from seeing it in person like this, isn't it?
That's for sure.
I wore this outfit when we were the same age.
So cute!
I don't think she wears this much.
Kimeshika
It's probably been a really long time.
It's true.
Yes, it's true.
So long!
We're not here anymore.
Oh...
Ah!
Oh! It's coming out!
It's coming from here!
That's great.
I miss it.
I miss it. Is this the one with the "Despair" dance? We used to dance like that.
Mini-Live
Mini-Live!
That's it!
Oh, no!
This uniform is so cute!
It's amazing to think that I have one of my own.
Yes, it is.
Your makeup is so deep.
It's summer!
Suki Rock?
Skylock.
Ah! It's Mr. Yakubou.
It really is.
Oh! It's so short!
Oh! You're right.
Not even close.
It's cute.
You're right.
It's so different when you look at it up close.
It's so cute!
This one looks like a piece of wood.
You're right.
Elele-lele, that's amazing!
It's so slanted!
Aah!
Oh, no!
It's too much!
It's so recent!
It's just recently.
Isn't this one with a lot of buttons?
Yes, so many buttons.
That's great.
Oh! I thought it wasn't closed yet.
Wow! I loved those uniforms.
I know.
Me too.
It's been a big part of my life lately.
I wore this a lot, too.
Ah! You wore this one, too, right?
That's right.
Yogo ribbons and all that.
Did you wear all the uniforms?
I've seen all of them.
Wow! That's amazing.
This is Kohaku.
Kohaku!
Wait, oh no!
I saw it!
I had the flu.
No, it wasn't.
I missed it.
It's cool.
It was so cool when it went around.
It was so cool.
I've never fallen out of the customary version.
It's sparkling.
It's true.
We did this for that one, didn't we?
Like a rose.
It's not a trigger. It's a good-bye.
It's pretty.
Do you have purple ones?
There was a purple one, too.
Purple doesn't make much of an impression on me.
There are a lot of red ones.
But they are both pretty.
They really look like roses.
I like this one.
Is this a Halloween event?
There's blood everywhere.
2014?
Wow! Oh no!
This is Budokan!
First time at Budokan.
Hot. My heart is hot.
What is this?
A stylish park?
It's so stylish.
It's true. It looks Chinese.
There it is.
Sun Wukong.
Sun Wukong?
The one Sanki wore when he went to Jingu.
You mean he called him Sun Wukong?
Yes.
It's a pair of pants.
These are pants?
I don't think it's a costume.
You look like you can play basketball.
I look like I can play basketball.
It's a nogi bingo!
That's great. I missed it.
I didn't know the article was like this.
Is it Ikuta-san?
It says "love.
Ikuta-san.
Let's ask questions to the fans.
Let's have a quiz.
This!
Who wore this outfit at what concert and when?
Please answer.
I seriously don't know.
I'll go get it.
As a hint.
It's Hinako Kitano's.
When was it?
I really don't know.
I'll ask Kitano-san.
Is this a clue?
High Speed 4.0
Isn't this bad?
What is this?
Wakatsuki-san.
It's true. I missed it.
This is Reika-chan.
Reika.
It's Jinggu.
Wow, that's great.
Rustling and rustling.
Mr. Takayama?
Ms. Takayama.
It's beautiful.
Sparkling.
Is this Manatsu-san's?
It's true.
I really like this one.
Is this Higuchi's?
It's Mr. Higuchi.
I wonder if I can touch it.
Oh, there's Mr. Otsuka.
He's too stylish.
This is amazing.
Lanze's is here, too.
It's so cute.
Lanze was wonderful.
It's amazing to see something like this.
It's amazing.
This block is like the title,
And the inner table.
There are costumes.
What a surprise.
Kulka.
You've been here before, right?
I've been here before.
Wait. I've never seen this before.
Is it a barge?
It's a music video.
It's amazing.
That wig and everything is amazing, isn't it?
The wig is amazing, isn't it?
This is a mannequin in school uniform.
I was so happy when I put it on.
I know.
This is Nishino-san's.
It's amazing that all the seniors who graduated are still here.
That's right.
This is,
Unrequited love.
Cute.
This is cute.
I like how it's a little transparent.
It's as it was born.
As it was born.
This is only for folded cotton, right?
There's not much left.
That's for sure.
Oh, it's mine.
I found Mukai-san over here, too.
You're kidding? Did you find it?
It's true.
It's Hoshino-san's from last year.
Ms. Hoshino has inherited it.
That's right. She's wearing it.
I'm close to Minami in height,
I'm often allowed to wear it.
I love it.
Oh, the sun,
Oh, it's from the sun.
I think this is the first time I've seen it in person.
Me neither.
Sundresses.
I've never seen it before.
I didn't know it was made of this kind of fabric.
It's denim fabric.
It's cute, isn't it?
Oh, it's a knock music video.
A knock music video.
Amazing.
You know everything, don't you?
I know everything.
I want to wear this.
Now.
It's beautiful. The color.
I want to wear it at the concert.
I wonder how it will look.
I want to wear it.
I want to wear it. I won't wear it.
Oh, it's goodbye.
Goodbye.
I've never had one of these.
It's too sacred.
It really is.
It's so nice.
Oh, Kana-san's.
This is the way home.
It's the way home.
It's so cute, isn't it?
I think I like the outfit of the way back the best.
You wore it, right?
I had her wear it.
What was I wearing it with?
Is it a new thing?
Newcomers?
Yes, it was.
It was nice.
Protective?
Protective color?
It's protective.
It's Shiraishi's protective color costume.
It's rare. Gentlemen.
Wow.
Did I get it right?
Look properly, everyone.
Look at it.
I love it.
I like you.
I like this one.
I love this one.
I know.
It looks good now.
Synchronize it.
It has wings on its back.
Amazing.
Yakubo gave it to me on Instagram or something,
I thought it was cute.
It's so cute. I love this outfit so much.
Oh, my God.
Hikki Rock, isn't it?
You took care of me on the tour, didn't you?
I wonder how many times I've worn it.
I've worn it a lot.
I was drenched by the rain.
It's true, isn't it? Drenched by the rain.
I wonder how it was washed?
Indeed.
It's amazing, isn't it?
You smelled the rain.
I thought it smelled like rain.
Denim is here.
The dry cleaning is here.
Like rice balls.
MV.
Yes, I was green in the music video.
I was Japanese green, wasn't I?
It's cute.
Isn't this one?
Denim.
It's amazing. It has all these decorations.
It's like Y2K.
What's this?
I wore it the other day.
M-dump Super Live.
This is the one I wore at the M-Dump.
Isn't this the latest?
I can't get enough of it.
I love it.
It's amazing. There's also this newest one.
It's amazing.
So many like this.
Thank you very much.
I heard that not all of them are here.
I see. There's more.
There's more.
I don't know what to do. What should I do?
Really, I'll wear it.
You're so cute.
Finished getting dressed.
Ta-da!
I'm all dressed up.
Do you understand?
I would like to introduce each of you one by one.
Okay.
Let's see....
What is this costume?
Yes, I'm wearing the polka-dot costume of Ms. Ikoma's solo song. I wore the polka-dot costume of Ikoma's solo song.
Please do it again.
Wow, that's great.
It's cute.
I'm so happy.
I thought I probably won't have a chance to wear it again,
I love polka dots, so I wore it.
It's cute.
I'm so happy.
It looks great on me.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
And the light blue color is very Hazuki-like,
Really? I'm glad.
Try changing into something else,
I was surprised to learn that you wear it like this.
It's split in two. Actually.
Yes, that's right.
I made some discoveries.
I'm very happy.
Cute.
Here's the new one.
She's so cute. She looks like a princess.
Really?
This is Ikoma's tight hugging outfit,
I don't think she wears it very often,
Only Ms. Ikoma wears it.
That's right.
So I took this opportunity to try it on.
It looks good on me.
From a distance, it looks like Ikoma.
What do you think? Fans.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
She is cute.
It looks like Ikoma-san.
I can't see her.
I can't see.
Thank you very much.
That's amazing. She is so cute.
I got to know Nogizaka because of Ikoma-san,
That's great.
I really like her,
I tried on this outfit today.
It's nice.
I tried on the Ikoma.
Cute.
I noticed that this is Ikoma from the period of unrequited love,
I don't think I have a chance to wear Ikoma in the past,
I came here to wear it,
Actually, this Ikoma is Mai Kudo's Ikoma.
It's so cute.
It must have been the right size.
I'm glad it fits perfectly.
Cute.
I'm going to get drunk.
I'm out.
Cute.
I'm very happy.
It looks good on me.
I'm happy.
So, I went to the costume warehouse today.
What did you think?
I was able to see the history of Nogizaka, and nostalgic costumes,
I used to be a geek, so I was really excited.
But we had a lot of fun too.
It was a lot of fun.
And you know what?
Did anyone notice?
No way.
First of all, here it is.
It's big!
Big!
Can you see it?
Do you know who this is?
It is Mr. Himura's.
It's huge!
It's amazing!
That's amazing.
It's amazing.
The costume designer said it can hold two people.
I'll probably put it in.
Wow.
Mr. Himura, you can wear it anytime.
You can wear it.
Please come again.
Please do.
The birthday concert will be held in a little while,
I'm sure the costumes you saw this time will be there,
Please find them.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!